<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Culture on Yﾄ》rﾄ［aya</title>
    <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/types/culture.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Culture on Yﾄ》rﾄ［aya</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 03:25:04 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/types/culture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Talkeetna : Alaskan Hinterland</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/talkeetna-alaskan-hinterland.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 03:25:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/talkeetna-alaskan-hinterland.html</guid>
      <description>As I walked the barely asphalted road that lead us from the well wooded section that closely guarded our hideout into what was the active and colorful part of the town, I started realizing why I liked this place so much. It was so much unlike the rest of the United States. There was an authentic small-town feel to it. Not the sterile and templated small-town that one gets used to in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkish Bath at a Hamam, Istanbul</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/hamam-at-istanbul-turkey.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 19:55:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/hamam-at-istanbul-turkey.html</guid>
      <description>After having spent two months backpacking and camping, the idea of a nice hot turkish bath seemed most desirable. Although I did not have a first hand experience about a Hamam, having read a few blogs about it, I felt I was bold enough to give it a try. Having been to Istanbul and not trying the Hamam was not acceptable for me. I kept putting it off for the first couple of days, with certain inhibitions taking hold of my cravings of a hot bath.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staying in a Cavehouse at Goreme, Cappadocia</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/goreme-cappadocia-homestay.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 19:32:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/goreme-cappadocia-homestay.html</guid>
      <description>Goreme was a beautiful town in a valley beyond the vast, brown mountains and the endless mounds of what looked like mud. That morning, we were transferred to a mini-bus after an overnight journey in a comfortable, large bus. We had got used to the efficiency of this country, and the general goodness of people, so we only had to step out of the bus and step into the smaller bus, without having to fuss about our luggages, which were perfectly tagged and transferred promptly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azaan at Sultanahmet, Istanbul</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/azaan-at-sultanahmet-istanbul.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 18:58:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/azaan-at-sultanahmet-istanbul.html</guid>
      <description>Walking the crowded streets of Sultanahmet late evening, I was trying to negotiate a road crossing, just as a tram passed the street. The wind was chill yet filled with the aroma of the food from the roadside restaurants. Just then, I heard the most melodious tune somewhere far, that made me freeze. I just stood there mesmerized, holding on to every single sound that came out from this singer. The words &amp;ldquo;Allahu Akhbar&amp;rdquo;, probably heard several times in my lifetime, had never before sounded so beautiful, so profound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Himalayan Hamlet : Kibber, Spiti Valley</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/kibber-a-himalayan-hamlet.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 15:34:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/kibber-a-himalayan-hamlet.html</guid>
      <description>Depending on what or who the source of information is, Kibber, an idyllic village that adorns the cold and silent Spiti Valley with its warm and bright coloured houses will rest in all sorts of record books. Needless to say, whether Kibber really hosted India&amp;rsquo;s highest post office or the rugged roadway that led us there should be considered for a motorcyclist bucketlist, it being the the highest motorable road, is all a matter of debate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When the entire village came dressed in their finery</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/entire-village-finery.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 16:16:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/entire-village-finery.html</guid>
      <description>We decided to visit the Kibber Gompa on a day when we heard there was an important event. Not knowing what it was about, we went along, with our camera ready. We were surprised to find almost the entire village there, young and the old, with more joining in. There was an air of festivity and cheer. Not knowing the language, we smiled at whoever our eyes met with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Music Bar at Goreme, Cappadocia, Turkey</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/live-music-bar-goreme.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 16:57:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/live-music-bar-goreme.html</guid>
      <description>The cold air was broken by the white trail of warm breath as I walked in the night. The bar was just a block away from where we stayed. The tables were only beginning to get filled up, when I realized that more people were coming in around the same time. We took a table for two, ordered some Raki, that came with some soft bread and dips. The lights were dim and created a warm, cozy atmosphere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A walk through Stone Town, Zanzibar</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/stonetown-zanzibar.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 19:02:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/stonetown-zanzibar.html</guid>
      <description>Just outside, you find yourself in a typical African town, with people getting about their routine work. There is traffic, pollution, vehicles honking, hawkers selling everything from bread, fruits, vegetables, newspaper to bags, shoes, clothes and people haggling for a good bargain; burqa clad school girls gossiping in small groups, giggling, waiting for their bus; high school boys trying to look like grown up men, wearing their traditional cap and gown, but their their school bags giving them away.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
