<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Multi Day on Yātrāmaya</title>
    <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/duration/multi-day.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Multi Day on Yātrāmaya</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 20:28:29 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/duration/multi-day/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Walking the Wadi Rum, Jordan</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/walking-the-wadi-rum-jordan.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 20:28:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/walking-the-wadi-rum-jordan.html</guid>
      <description>How far would have to drive out to actually get somewhere? Strange were my thoughts as we stared out of the SUV into the emptiness all arouund. Did we really have to get anywhere at all? In a desert like Wadi Rum it took only an hour worth of driving to get to a point where one&amp;rsquo;s source and destination started to look the same and considering we did not have any specific goal it was only logical to rely on our host who was intently driving onwards on a trail that could not have been older than a week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staying in a Cavehouse at Goreme, Cappadocia</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/goreme-cappadocia-homestay.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 19:32:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/goreme-cappadocia-homestay.html</guid>
      <description>Goreme was a beautiful town in a valley beyond the vast, brown mountains and the endless mounds of what looked like mud. That morning, we were transferred to a mini-bus after an overnight journey in a comfortable, large bus. We had got used to the efficiency of this country, and the general goodness of people, so we only had to step out of the bus and step into the smaller bus, without having to fuss about our luggages, which were perfectly tagged and transferred promptly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Himalayan Hamlet : Kibber, Spiti Valley</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/kibber-a-himalayan-hamlet.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 15:34:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/kibber-a-himalayan-hamlet.html</guid>
      <description>Depending on what or who the source of information is, Kibber, an idyllic village that adorns the cold and silent Spiti Valley with its warm and bright coloured houses will rest in all sorts of record books. Needless to say, whether Kibber really hosted India&amp;rsquo;s highest post office or the rugged roadway that led us there should be considered for a motorcyclist bucketlist, it being the the highest motorable road, is all a matter of debate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staying in a remote East Ugandan Village, Africa</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/homestay-experience-bududa.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 11:16:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/homestay-experience-bududa.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Is it true that women will be burnt alive for dowry in India?&amp;rdquo; Mai asked with her fear in her eyes and her palm covering her mouth. She did not mean to offend me. The innocence in her voice and her genuine concern for her sisters in India made me offer a simple, plain answer. &amp;ldquo;Yes, it does happen even now in some villages, although it is not legal&amp;rdquo; I tried to calm her down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camping next to Savage river, Denali National Park</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/camping-at-savage-river.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 10:32:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/camping-at-savage-river.html</guid>
      <description>The weather was perfect when we entered Denali. The sun was bright and our bus made a special stop on the way to see the majestic mountain because it is not everyday that she presents herself in such glorious view. After completing the mandatory registration and collecting the campsite markers, I got on the park bus that would take me to the campsite, Savage River. It was the farthest point in the park route that allows private vehicles, although we were not driving, so took the bus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My adventures with Matatus</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/adventures-with-matatus.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 19:32:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/adventures-with-matatus.html</guid>
      <description>Before travelling to East Africa, I had managed my travels with two grand assumptions (a) long distances are better covered by night (b) if you are ready to pay a price, there are better options in public transport. While these two were busted pretty quickly, none of my experiences so far had prepared me for a “matatu”.
From whatever I had read earlier, before landing in Kenya, I had deduced that all my travels had to be done during the day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Trek to Kuari Pass and Pangarchulla, Uttarakhand</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/trek-to-kuari-pass-pangarchulla.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 19:32:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/trek-to-kuari-pass-pangarchulla.html</guid>
      <description>My back was unaccustomed to the heavy load. It was more than a year since I had been on any serious multi-day hike. And, even though we had hired a couple of porters and a guide to carry the camping equipment and the cooking essentials, even the personal items that I had signed up to haul was seeming heavier than I had imagined. The moment I got out of the jeep and started walking through the narrow lanes of the village Dhak, two thoughts were on my mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A walk through Stone Town, Zanzibar</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/stonetown-zanzibar.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 19:02:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/stonetown-zanzibar.html</guid>
      <description>Just outside, you find yourself in a typical African town, with people getting about their routine work. There is traffic, pollution, vehicles honking, hawkers selling everything from bread, fruits, vegetables, newspaper to bags, shoes, clothes and people haggling for a good bargain; burqa clad school girls gossiping in small groups, giggling, waiting for their bus; high school boys trying to look like grown up men, wearing their traditional cap and gown, but their their school bags giving them away.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
