<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Half Day on Yﾄ》rﾄ［aya</title>
    <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/duration/half-day.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Half Day on Yﾄ》rﾄ［aya</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 03:25:04 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/duration/half-day/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Talkeetna : Alaskan Hinterland</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/talkeetna-alaskan-hinterland.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 03:25:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/talkeetna-alaskan-hinterland.html</guid>
      <description>As I walked the barely asphalted road that lead us from the well wooded section that closely guarded our hideout into what was the active and colorful part of the town, I started realizing why I liked this place so much. It was so much unlike the rest of the United States. There was an authentic small-town feel to it. Not the sterile and templated small-town that one gets used to in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkish Bath at a Hamam, Istanbul</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/hamam-at-istanbul-turkey.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 19:55:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/hamam-at-istanbul-turkey.html</guid>
      <description>After having spent two months backpacking and camping, the idea of a nice hot turkish bath seemed most desirable. Although I did not have a first hand experience about a Hamam, having read a few blogs about it, I felt I was bold enough to give it a try. Having been to Istanbul and not trying the Hamam was not acceptable for me. I kept putting it off for the first couple of days, with certain inhibitions taking hold of my cravings of a hot bath.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azaan at Sultanahmet, Istanbul</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/azaan-at-sultanahmet-istanbul.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 18:58:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/azaan-at-sultanahmet-istanbul.html</guid>
      <description>Walking the crowded streets of Sultanahmet late evening, I was trying to negotiate a road crossing, just as a tram passed the street. The wind was chill yet filled with the aroma of the food from the roadside restaurants. Just then, I heard the most melodious tune somewhere far, that made me freeze. I just stood there mesmerized, holding on to every single sound that came out from this singer. The words &amp;ldquo;Allahu Akhbar&amp;rdquo;, probably heard several times in my lifetime, had never before sounded so beautiful, so profound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bentota to Colombo by train, Sri Lanka</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/bentota-to-colombo-train-srilanka.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2021 20:23:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/bentota-to-colombo-train-srilanka.html</guid>
      <description>Local train journey in Sri Lanka is a must do to see the culture up close. And, what&amp;rsquo;s better than the coastal rail route that offers some breathtaking views of the coast as well. Our started at this quaint little station called Bentota.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glacier Tour, Seward, Alaska</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/glacier-tour-seward.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/glacier-tour-seward.html</guid>
      <description>A bald eagle swooped in very close to our boat as we set off. The sun was struggling to shine through the dense grey clouds that threatened to pour down anytime. To be sailing off into the icy cold waters of the Pacific, with limited visibility, in the hope of seeing some glaciers, started to seem a bit ambitious. The misty cold morning confined most of us to the cozy interior of the boat, with little to look forward to other than this bald eagle and a friendly otter that did not seem to mind either our boat or the ice cold water.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When the entire village came dressed in their finery</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/entire-village-finery.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 16:16:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/entire-village-finery.html</guid>
      <description>We decided to visit the Kibber Gompa on a day when we heard there was an important event. Not knowing what it was about, we went along, with our camera ready. We were surprised to find almost the entire village there, young and the old, with more joining in. There was an air of festivity and cheer. Not knowing the language, we smiled at whoever our eyes met with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whale Watching at Mirissa, Sri Lanka</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/whale-watching-lanka.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 17:13:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/whale-watching-lanka.html</guid>
      <description>This was nothing close to what I had ever imagined. The boat was rather small. The waves were menacingly rough, challenging to throw the boat off balance at the slightest opportunity. There were about 20 people on the boat, most of them in various stages of sea sickness. The lucky ones, like myself, who were miraculously unaffected by the rough sea, were on the deck with our eyes glued to the waters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Music Bar at Goreme, Cappadocia, Turkey</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/live-music-bar-goreme.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 16:57:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/live-music-bar-goreme.html</guid>
      <description>The cold air was broken by the white trail of warm breath as I walked in the night. The bar was just a block away from where we stayed. The tables were only beginning to get filled up, when I realized that more people were coming in around the same time. We took a table for two, ordered some Raki, that came with some soft bread and dips. The lights were dim and created a warm, cozy atmosphere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An unforgettable encounter with our closest cousin</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/our-closest-cousin.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 19:17:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/our-closest-cousin.html</guid>
      <description>It is unmistakably the most beautiful place we would be staying in our entire trip. I could spend hours just looking at these mountains, the rainforests and never cease to be amazed by their existence, being drawn into them further and further with every passing moment. I could be lost momentarily in mundane tasks like eating or washing clothes or fussing about the ants; but the presence of the mountains constantly pulls me into a trance every now and then.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Andaman Forest Walk</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/andaman-forest-walk.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2014 12:31:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/andaman-forest-walk.html</guid>
      <description>Neil Island being one of the smaller ones of the Andaman archipelago is an inconspicuous dot in the vast blue waters of the mighty Indian Ocean. Here one gets the sensation of being &amp;lsquo;bound&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;limited&amp;rsquo; by the land area. Getting to experience both sunrise and sunset on the same day was something that I looked forward to on small islands and Neil had not disappointed me in that respect and more.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
