<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Full Day on Yﾄ》rﾄ［aya</title>
    <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/duration/full-day.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Full Day on Yﾄ》rﾄ［aya</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 19:33:32 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/duration/full-day/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A walk through Sinharaja Forest Reserve, Srilanka</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/sinharaja-forest-reserve-srilanka.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 19:33:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/sinharaja-forest-reserve-srilanka.html</guid>
      <description>I had imagined this drop-shaped island country always to have been green; a green dot floating in the endless blue waters of the mighty Indian Ocean. I would like to believe that it was once covered with dense, impenetrable tropical rainforests, with inneumerable waterfalls, countless streams flowing through. It was as though in an effort to recreate this lost experience, this missed opportunity, that I chose to trek through the Sinharaja Forest Reserve as one of my first experiences in Sri Lanka.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manali to Kaza by Bus</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/manali-to-kaza-by-bus.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 18:24:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/manali-to-kaza-by-bus.html</guid>
      <description>Everything looks brown here, the roads, the walls, the houses and of course the surrounding mountains, that never fail to establish their mammoth presence, constantly. It soon became my favorite past time to see the miniature buses, trucks, motorbikes moving like tiny insects along the narrow lines drawn along these huge mountains, pitting bigger and bigger vehicles against these huge rocks and then ridiculing their minuscule presence. The mountains silently reminded me of the fragility of our existence, the unsaid whispers through which they conveyed how they had seen life come and go, in an instant, in their time-lines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wildlife Viewing in Denali National Park</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/wildlife-viewing-denali.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 16:16:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/wildlife-viewing-denali.html</guid>
      <description>We got onto the transit bus to Wonder Lake, one of the farthest campgrounds inside the Denali National park. Springtime being good tourist season, the bus was full and we managed to occupy the last second row. With my camera ready, I glued my eyes to the window of the bus, carefully scanning the vast landscape for any movement</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Denali at her raw best</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/denali-at-her-raw-best.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 10:17:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/denali-at-her-raw-best.html</guid>
      <description>Sitting in the park bus, we felt as though we were on a private tour of Denali, just 4 of us, and our guide cum driver, Nick. By afternoon the entire Denali range was covered by thick clouds, it had started to get dark, our chances of spotting wildlife also diminished with the daylight. With the rain looming on the horizon, we almost had the entire park for ourselves. Driving through thick fog, with our headlights on, with almost no visibility, the raw beauty of Denali, the vast river plains, the mountains showed us yet another side, which was entirely different from what we had seen the previous day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stuck in Serengeti</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/stuck-in-serengeti.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 19:47:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/stuck-in-serengeti.html</guid>
      <description>At this point, I knew we were not getting anywhere. We were in the middle of wilderness with a vehicle that refused to move and nobody in sight for miles to even ask for assistance. As the driver got out of the vehicle to collect more logs, I was thinking about the lions we just saw and how they might have sensed that a human being was walking around. They could be watching us from a distance and tracking our movements.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
