<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nature on Yﾄ》rﾄ［aya</title>
    <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/types/nature.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nature on Yﾄ》rﾄ［aya</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 20:28:29 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/types/nature/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Walking the Wadi Rum, Jordan</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/walking-the-wadi-rum-jordan.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 20:28:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/walking-the-wadi-rum-jordan.html</guid>
      <description>How far would have to drive out to actually get somewhere? Strange were my thoughts as we stared out of the SUV into the emptiness all arouund. Did we really have to get anywhere at all? In a desert like Wadi Rum it took only an hour worth of driving to get to a point where one&amp;rsquo;s source and destination started to look the same and considering we did not have any specific goal it was only logical to rely on our host who was intently driving onwards on a trail that could not have been older than a week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glacier Tour, Seward, Alaska</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/glacier-tour-seward.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/glacier-tour-seward.html</guid>
      <description>A bald eagle swooped in very close to our boat as we set off. The sun was struggling to shine through the dense grey clouds that threatened to pour down anytime. To be sailing off into the icy cold waters of the Pacific, with limited visibility, in the hope of seeing some glaciers, started to seem a bit ambitious. The misty cold morning confined most of us to the cozy interior of the boat, with little to look forward to other than this bald eagle and a friendly otter that did not seem to mind either our boat or the ice cold water.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wildlife Viewing in Denali National Park</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/wildlife-viewing-denali.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 16:16:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/wildlife-viewing-denali.html</guid>
      <description>We got onto the transit bus to Wonder Lake, one of the farthest campgrounds inside the Denali National park. Springtime being good tourist season, the bus was full and we managed to occupy the last second row. With my camera ready, I glued my eyes to the window of the bus, carefully scanning the vast landscape for any movement</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camping next to Savage river, Denali National Park</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/camping-at-savage-river.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 10:32:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/camping-at-savage-river.html</guid>
      <description>The weather was perfect when we entered Denali. The sun was bright and our bus made a special stop on the way to see the majestic mountain because it is not everyday that she presents herself in such glorious view. After completing the mandatory registration and collecting the campsite markers, I got on the park bus that would take me to the campsite, Savage River. It was the farthest point in the park route that allows private vehicles, although we were not driving, so took the bus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Denali at her raw best</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/denali-at-her-raw-best.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 10:17:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/denali-at-her-raw-best.html</guid>
      <description>Sitting in the park bus, we felt as though we were on a private tour of Denali, just 4 of us, and our guide cum driver, Nick. By afternoon the entire Denali range was covered by thick clouds, it had started to get dark, our chances of spotting wildlife also diminished with the daylight. With the rain looming on the horizon, we almost had the entire park for ourselves. Driving through thick fog, with our headlights on, with almost no visibility, the raw beauty of Denali, the vast river plains, the mountains showed us yet another side, which was entirely different from what we had seen the previous day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stuck in Serengeti</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/stuck-in-serengeti.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 19:47:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/stuck-in-serengeti.html</guid>
      <description>At this point, I knew we were not getting anywhere. We were in the middle of wilderness with a vehicle that refused to move and nobody in sight for miles to even ask for assistance. As the driver got out of the vehicle to collect more logs, I was thinking about the lions we just saw and how they might have sensed that a human being was walking around. They could be watching us from a distance and tracking our movements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An unforgettable encounter with our closest cousin</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/our-closest-cousin.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 19:17:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/our-closest-cousin.html</guid>
      <description>It is unmistakably the most beautiful place we would be staying in our entire trip. I could spend hours just looking at these mountains, the rainforests and never cease to be amazed by their existence, being drawn into them further and further with every passing moment. I could be lost momentarily in mundane tasks like eating or washing clothes or fussing about the ants; but the presence of the mountains constantly pulls me into a trance every now and then.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
