<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Roadtrip on Yātrāmaya</title>
    <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/types/roadtrip.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Roadtrip on Yātrāmaya</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 18:24:04 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/types/roadtrip/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Manali to Kaza by Bus</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/manali-to-kaza-by-bus.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 18:24:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/manali-to-kaza-by-bus.html</guid>
      <description>Everything looks brown here, the roads, the walls, the houses and of course the surrounding mountains, that never fail to establish their mammoth presence, constantly. It soon became my favorite past time to see the miniature buses, trucks, motorbikes moving like tiny insects along the narrow lines drawn along these huge mountains, pitting bigger and bigger vehicles against these huge rocks and then ridiculing their minuscule presence. The mountains silently reminded me of the fragility of our existence, the unsaid whispers through which they conveyed how they had seen life come and go, in an instant, in their time-lines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My adventures with Matatus</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/adventures-with-matatus.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 19:32:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/adventures-with-matatus.html</guid>
      <description>Before travelling to East Africa, I had managed my travels with two grand assumptions (a) long distances are better covered by night (b) if you are ready to pay a price, there are better options in public transport. While these two were busted pretty quickly, none of my experiences so far had prepared me for a “matatu”.
From whatever I had read earlier, before landing in Kenya, I had deduced that all my travels had to be done during the day.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
