<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2017 on Yﾄ》rﾄ［aya</title>
    <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/year/2017.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2017 on Yﾄ》rﾄ［aya</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 15:34:20 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/year/2017/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Himalayan Hamlet : Kibber, Spiti Valley</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/kibber-a-himalayan-hamlet.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 15:34:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/kibber-a-himalayan-hamlet.html</guid>
      <description>Depending on what or who the source of information is, Kibber, an idyllic village that adorns the cold and silent Spiti Valley with its warm and bright coloured houses will rest in all sorts of record books. Needless to say, whether Kibber really hosted India&amp;rsquo;s highest post office or the rugged roadway that led us there should be considered for a motorcyclist bucketlist, it being the the highest motorable road, is all a matter of debate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manali to Kaza by Bus</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/manali-to-kaza-by-bus.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 18:24:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/manali-to-kaza-by-bus.html</guid>
      <description>Everything looks brown here, the roads, the walls, the houses and of course the surrounding mountains, that never fail to establish their mammoth presence, constantly. It soon became my favorite past time to see the miniature buses, trucks, motorbikes moving like tiny insects along the narrow lines drawn along these huge mountains, pitting bigger and bigger vehicles against these huge rocks and then ridiculing their minuscule presence. The mountains silently reminded me of the fragility of our existence, the unsaid whispers through which they conveyed how they had seen life come and go, in an instant, in their time-lines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When the entire village came dressed in their finery</title>
      <link>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/entire-village-finery.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 16:16:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yatramaya.hoatz.in/experiences/entire-village-finery.html</guid>
      <description>We decided to visit the Kibber Gompa on a day when we heard there was an important event. Not knowing what it was about, we went along, with our camera ready. We were surprised to find almost the entire village there, young and the old, with more joining in. There was an air of festivity and cheer. Not knowing the language, we smiled at whoever our eyes met with.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
